So hai vimaan welcome to our channel welcome to you
as you all know that I had an
accident on 27th of March so
regarding that I had also given a Twitter post
so you guys sent a lot of sir best
special so I am probably
recovering from that and thank you thank
you but Jo D best precious for you we are here so we are
making more videos as well and everything is
going well so let me
tell you how the accident happened I am late so I was going to office by
driving my vehicle i.e. Ola electric scooter then
an auto came in front and I had to press the brake immediately
and I don't know why the
wheels got locked and I fell on this side
left side so because of falling on the left side
this hand got hurt a lot so that's why
you can still see this
in the question so yes I had to go to the hospital
for dressing that is to dress my cut
or to get this
thing fitted but my
Ola also had to be sent to the hospital that is it had to be
sent to the service center so  Now
in this video we will know that if any Ola passenger meets with an
accident then
what action does Ola take on it, that is, how does the
insurance team of Ola, that is,
how does the team that looks after the insurance respond
or how does Ola respond to such a company,
how much money will you have to pay on you, still, that is, even if you have
insurance,
then you will know all this in this video, so
this video is going to be very informative, so please
watch this video till the end, so
now let us know what
benefits I have from Ola, so
first of all, insurance is there
in every vehicle, whether it is a two wheeler
or a four wheeler, then that is there, along with that I also have
Ola Care Class
and I also have Ola's extended
warranty, so obviously
my vehicle has met with an accident,
so obviously I had to
claim the insurance, so to know what is its process, I
first went to Ola's
customer care yesterday and they said that  Everyone has the
customer care numbers now,
everyone knows it, so
after calling the customer care yesterday, I came to know that the customer
told me that I have to go to the app, so I did the same, I went to the
Ola app and raised
a ticket, you can see on the
screen how to raise this ticket, so
I raised this ticket on 27th March,
but it was showing that on 30th
March, someone from my house will come and
take this scooter to the service centre, so
seeing this I was a little disappointed
because why should I keep my car at
home for three days, I mean I could
n't even get the car repaired, in fact the car was
running, it is not that it was
not in a condition to run, the car was
running well but the panels were damaged
as you can see on the screen,
anyway, I called a guy from the
service centre yesterday, I had his number, so
they responded well
and they sent a guy  I asked him to take
my car but in Hindi I mean at that
time I got a WhatsApp message and there was
a link in that message, by
clicking on the link I had to upload some documents
or give some details, so to
fill this form you will have to first give your email ID,
then you will have to give your mobile number here,
again they are asking for email ID, so you will have to
give email ID as well, so whether it is plus
or not, you will have to enter that as well, what is your complaint
number, then you will have to go to
next, going to next
you will also have to give the vehicle registration number, whether the
car was parked or not, yes no, the
most important thing
you will get at the end is the
claim number, so I had to generate the claim number by calling 1800 to 666, so I have
insurance with this, so I have to
call on this number,
if your relative is x or it is digital then
you can ask by calling on this number,
anyway an IVR will be turned on, it will
instruct you on how to generate this claim
number, so after generating the claim number
You can note it down and put it here.
Then on the next page, by
clicking next, you will get the documents that I
said, PAN card, Aadhar card, policy
document, then you will have to upload all these documents
there, then
click on the submit button. So, yes, you have reached
this part of the video, so please
like this video and
subscribe to our channel. If maximum viewers have
not subscribed to our channel, then
please subscribe to our channel
because this gives us a lot of support and
also motivates us to make the next video. So,
my suggestion for you people is
that you should keep these five things in your phone - PAN
card, Aadhar card, copy of your RC book,
copy of driving license and
copy of insurance,
because
if such an unfortunate incident ever happens, then
you can start the insurance process as soon as possible.
I received a WhatsApp message from Ola's
insurance team, there was a
link there, so by clicking on the link, I
again got the documents from the documents and
details from the file.  I had to add it up,
along with the claim idea, which is the
claim ID starting with MOT. I
also had to enter it there.
After submitting that, a PF form was sent to me.
In that PF form, it was mentioned
which parts would be
taxed by the insurance company and which
parts would not be taxed by the insurance company. You
can see that PF form on the screen right now.
It was a bit scary and strange
because what was visible there, which is
considered a cross, you can see that
if they total it, that is, crosswise, which is
not taxed by the insurance company, then it would go
above 10,000.
Seeing this, I felt a bit strange that
despite having insurance, why would I have to pay 10,000
rupees. By then, it was 31st of March.
Next, on the first
of April, I had to go to the service center with a friend of mine
because his
front foot was going to be changed.
I have shot a detailed video related to it,
so you can see the
link to it in the description box.  So that day I
went and saw that no work has
started on my car, so I saw it and it seemed a
bit strange to me, so I asked those
people, that is the insurance people, that
why the work has not started on my car yet, they said
that the approval has not come yet completely, that is why the work has
not started yet,
then I told them that you
see, one of the cracks here is the
projector lamp, the heat lamp,
I had to change that because
you can see there, now you can also see on the screen
that there is a
crack type thing, so it was bothering me a bit
because that crack can
flood in the future, so I
tried to convince these people that get this
head lamp changed
otherwise this problem can arise later,
water can also enter during the rain, it can get damaged
even today, a lot can happen,
so I said this type of thing, then they
suggested me to give the number of a person, that is, the
number of the person who is the insurance agent of this  It was given to me earlier, so I called
him on the number and told
him that please arrange it for me, then
this was very helpful, then
he told me that this does not happen,
but it is the first time, so they can
consider 80%, so
I will get 80% from the insurance company, but
I will have to pay the remaining 20% ​​from my side,
I agreed, I did not have any option,
match match like, so anyone, this was on the
third of April, that is, Monday,
then on Friday, that is, on the 7th
of April, I received a message from the
insurance team of Ola, there was
a car code in the WhatsApp message, so I had to
scan the car code and make the payment,
and along with that, some ID or some other
details were sent to me, so
I asked these people how much payment I have to make,
this was not mentioned, actually,
other brother, it was a bit funny too, so
I called these people and asked
how much payment I have to make, then they said that whatever  There
is 20% of the head lamp, that 20% has to be
paid, so that amount was ₹2500, so
I scanned the car code and made the
payment, then these
people asked me whether you have Care
Plus or not, so I
said yes brother, I have Care Plus, so I
asked these people why do you need Care Plus right now, then
these people said that if you do
not have Care Plus then you will have to pay ₹800,
which means
you will have to pay ₹800 for pickup and drop,
if you do not have Care Plus, then
you can see that the
issues of the panels here, the damaged panels,
all of them have been
replaced properly, there is no issue till now,
so I also took the car for a little
round, there is no issue with this car, there is no
sound, nothing, so
yes, I am very impressed with the service of Ola, that is, the
service I got after the accident,
and the
insurance team of Ola, which is  Everything has been done
well, after
talking to ICC Prudential, I am very impressed with them too and I
said thumbs up and what has been your experience with Ola
's service or if you have
faced any such unfortunate incident then
how has Ola responded to you
or how has it addressed your problems,
please do tell us in the comment box, so if you guys have liked this video so far then
please
like this video, if
you like it then please
subscribe to our channel if you have not done so yet
and share this video as much as possible, it
is very important to share this
video so that other people get help,
they also get to know
what action should be taken if such an incident happens, so and
now let's go bye bye